Guide to the New York University Archives Collection of Publications and Ephemera MC.334
New York University Archives
- RG 8.2.1. Office of Work-Life Services, 1998-2004
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1998-2004 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Education Program Guide Booklets, 1999-2002 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- RG 8.2.2. Faculty / Staff Assistance Program, 1997-2006
  - The FrontLine Supervisor, 2000-2003 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1997-2006 (Box 65, Folder 7-8)
- RG 8.2.3. Family Care, 2008-2011
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2008-2011 (Box 65, Folder 9)
- RG 8.3. Protection Services / Department of Public Safety, 1986-1990, 2005-2010
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1986-1990 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1992, 1997-1998 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2005-2010 (Box 65, Folder 11, Box 66, Folder 1)
- RG 8.4. Purchasing Services; Division of Administrative and Purchasing Services, 1978-2013
  - Dollars and Sense, 1991-2013 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Procedure Guides and Manuals, 1978-2000s (Box 66, Folder 3-7)
- RG 9.0. Office of Academic Development, 1990-1996
  - Vniversity, 1961-1996 (Box 67, Folder 1-8, Box 103)
- RG 9.3. Academic Planning and Services, undated
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, undated (Box 68, Folder 1)
- RG 9.4. Research Services / Sponsored Programs, 1960-ongoing
  - Research News, May 2014-ongoing
    Initially published as a digest, Research News provides news on research, awards, and ideas being produced by all members of the NYU community.
  - Sponsored Programs Newsletter, 1979-1984 (Box 68, Folder 2-6)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Sponsored Research Booklets, 1960-1973 (Box 68, Folder 7-10, Box 69, Folder 1-4)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1970-2002 (Box 69, Folder 5-6)
- RG 9.5.1. Humanities Council, 1977-2002
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1977-2002 (Box 70, Folder 1-8, Box 71, Folder 1-6)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Event Listings Posters, 1977-1992 (Box 102, Folder 1-4)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 1974-2004 (Box 102, Folder 5-6, Box 103, Folder 9)
- RG 9.5.2. Humanities Exchange Program, undated
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, undated (Box 71, Folder 7)
- RG 9.5.4. Curricular Development Challenge Fund, 1985-2002
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1985-2002 (Box 71, Folder 8-9)
- RG 9.5.5. Faculty Resource Network, 1991-2000
  - A Poetry Collection, 1984-2002 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Resource Network, 1992-2000 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Network, 1988-2002 (Box 72, Folder 1-3)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1984-2000 (Box 72, Folder 4-7)
- RG 9.8. Institute of African American Affairs, 1970-2004
  - Black Creation, 1970-1975 (Box 72, Folder 8, Box 73, Folder 1-3)
  - Brownstone, 1982-2004 (Box 73, Folder 4-7, Box 74, Folder 1-5, Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Creative Forces, 1978-1979 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - IAAA Student Brief, 1986-1987 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Institute of Afro-American Affairs Newsletter, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Sojourner, 1970-1971 (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - The Third Eye, 1978 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1969-2004 (Box 75, Folder 1-5)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 1987-1991 (Box 103, Folder 11)
- RG 9.9. Department of Athletics, circa 2018
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, circa 2018 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- RG 9.10.3. ITS – Administrative Computing Services, 2000-ongoing
  - Connect, 2008-2014 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Connect: Information Technology at NYU, November 2015-November 2021
    Connect: IT at NYU is a publication of Information Technology Services (ITS) that reports on the ways that faculty, staff and students at the University use computing and networking in support of their research, administration, and pedagogy. In the spring of 2011, Connect began publishing exclusively to the Web. In 2020, Connect changed its name to the Download.
  - The Download, May 2022-ongoing
    The Download is a publication of NYU Information Technology (NYU IT) that reports on the many innovative and engaging ways faculty, staff, and students at New York University use computing, networking, and other IT technologies in support of their research, administration, and pedagogy.
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2000-2008 (Box 75, Folder 8)
- RG 9.11. League of World Universities, 1997, 2001
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1997, 2001 (Box 75, Folder 9)
- RG 9.12. La Pietra, 1997, 2006
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1997, 2006 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- RG 9.13. Global U, undated
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, undated (Box 76, Folder 2)
- RG 9.14. Africa House, 2006-2015
  Historical Note
  Africa House is an interdisciplinary institute at NYU devoted to the study of contemporary Africa, focusing on Political, Social, and Economic Development.
  - Africa House Facebook, May 2014-May 2015
    The Facebook page contains posts related to the PEN World Voices Festival of International Literature, the Africa Economic Forum, the Africa Region Meeting of the Econometric Society, job announcements, and other events.
  - Africa House Twitter, May 2014-May 2015
    The Twitter feed contains tweets about the NYU Africa Forum, Stern in Africa, PEN World Voices Festival of International Literature, travel in Africa, and other events.
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2006-2007 (Box 76, Folder 3)
- RG 10.2. Office of the Bursar, 1999-2006
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Understanding Your Statement Booklets, 1999-2006 (Box 76, Folder 4-9)
- RG 10.4. Office of the Controller, 1988, 2005
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1988, 2005 (Box 76, Folder 10-11)
- RG 10.5. Financial Systems, 1997-2012
  - Financial System Redesign Project, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Fame, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2012 (Box 76, Folder 14)
- RG 11.1. Academic Facilities, undated
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, undated (Box 76, Folder 15)
- RG 11.5. Faculty Housing, 2007
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2007 (Box 76, Folder 16)
- RG 12.0. Office of VP of Student Affairs / Office of Senior VP Enrollment Services and Planning, 1967-ongoing
  - Newsletter of All-Square Student Affairs, 1967-1969 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Open Space, 1977, 1979-1980 (Box 77, Folder 2, Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Parent and Family Newsletter, May 2022-ongoing
    The Parent and Family Newsletter is produced by the Center for Student Life and provides helpful information relative to parents of students currently enrolled at NYU in New York.
  - Parents e-Newsletter, May 2014-ongoing
    The Parents e-Newsletter is produced by NYU's Center for Student Life on a monthly basis to provide parents regular updates on happens in the NYU community. The newsletter contains contents related to enrollment, admitted students, parent's weekend, graduation, career development, on campus dining, on campus housing, and other news.
  - Transitions, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1969-2011 (Box 77, Folder 4-12)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1987-1988 (Box 104, Folder 2)
- RG 12.2. Office of Senior VP for Student Affairs, 1990
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 1990 (Box 104, Folder 3)
- RG 12.2.1. Placement Services / Career and Industry Placement / Career Planning and Placement/Office of Career Services, 1917-1925, 1960-1994
  - Career Connection, 1988-1990 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - The Career Planning Placement Weekly, 1986-1988 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Careers, Careers, 1986-1990 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Placement Services Bulletin, 1968-1972 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Placement Services Newsletter, 1970-1972 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1917-1925, 1960-1994 (Box 78, Folder 1-9)
- RG 12.2.2. Student Employment Office / The Wasserman Center for Career Development, 1980s, 2006-2010
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1980s, 2006-2010 (Box 78, Folder 10-11)
- RG 12.2.3. Office of Global Services, 1954-2008
  - 41 Degrees, 74 Degrees, 2000-2001 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Expressions, 2008 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - The International Newsletter, 1984-1989 (Box 79, Folder 1-2)
  - International Student Center Bulletin, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - InternationaLink, 2004-2008 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1954-2008 (Box 79, Folder 5-9)
- RG 12.2.3.1. Paths to Peace Program (2007-2016), 2014-2016
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- History Booklet, 2016 (Box 79, Folder 10-11)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, circa 2014-2016 (Box 79, Folder 12)
- RG 12.2.4. Jeffrey S. Gould Welcome Center, 1987-2007
  - NYU SyntheSIS, 1989 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1987-1988, 2007, undated (Box 80, Folder 2-3)
- RG 12.2.5. Loeb Student Center, 1959-2010
  - Loeb Student Center Weekly Calendar of Events, 1966-1968 (Box 80, Folder 4-8)
  - Summer Session News of the Week, 1961, 1964 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1959-1998, undated (Box 80, Folder 9-10, Box 81, Folder 1-13, Box 82, Folder 1-9)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 1980s-1990s, undated (Box 48, Folder 6, Box 51, Folder 8, Box 104, Folder 5)
- RG 12.2.6. Student Activity Board / Student Activities Office / Center for Student Activities, Leadership, and Service, 1987-2011, undated
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1987-2011, undated (Box 83, Folder 1-9, Box 84, Folder 1-4)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 2000-2009 (Box 104, Folder 6)
- RG 12.2.7. Disabled Student Services / Henry and Lucy Moses Center for Students with Disabilities, 1980-2004
  The title of this series was retained due to its historical context.
  - Access NYU / NYU Access, 1985-1999 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - CSD Today: Faculty Edition, 2003-2004 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Update, 1982-1985 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1980-2003 (Box 85, Folder 1-7)
- RG 12.2.8. University Dining Services, 1986-2007
  - Dining News, 1986-1988 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1987-2007 (Box 85, Folder 9-11)
- RG 12.2.11. Wellness Exchange, 2004-2007
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 1989, circa 2004-2006 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2004-2007 (Box 85, Folder 12-13)
- RG 12.2.12. Kimmel Center for University Life, circa 2018
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, circa 2018 (Box 86, Folder 1)
- RG 12.2.12.1. NYU Kimmel Galleries, 2013
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2013 (Box 86, Folder 2)
- RG 12.3. Admissions Office, 1933-2020
  - For Juniors: NYU / NYU News for Juniors, 2000-2010 (Box 105, Folder 4-6)
  - New York University Connections, circa 2002-2003 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - New York University Newsletter, 1959, 1963-1964 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - New York University Parents News International, 2000-2002 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - New York University Parent's News, 1999-2006 (Box 105, Folder 2-3)
  - New York University Student News for International Student, 1999-2003 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - New York University Student News / NYU Student News, 1999-2004 (Box 86, Folder 6-7)
  - New York University Today, 1986-1988 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - NYU News, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - NYU News for Parents, 2006-2010 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - NYU Preview News / NYU PreView, circa 1999-2006 (Box 86, Folder 9-10)
  - NYU Quarterly / NYU Q, 2010-2018, undated (Box 86, Folder 11-13, Box 87, Folder 1)
  - N.Y.U. Today / New York University Today, circa 1978-1983 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Parents' News, circa 1989-2000 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Parents' Newsletter, 1979-1984 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1933-1934 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1967-2015 (Box 87, Folder 5-10, Box 88, Folder 1-10, Box 89, Folder 1-8)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 2002-2020 (Box 48, Folder 7, Box 51, Folder 9, Box 104, Folder 8-10)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2007-2011 (Box 90, Folder 1-7, Box 91, Folder 1-6)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2011-2016 (Box 92, Folder 1-6, Box 93)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2016-2020 (Box 94, Folder 1-6, Box 430, Folder 4)
- RG 12.3.1. NYU CALI (College Access Leadership Institute), 2018
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2018 (Box 94, Folder 7)
- RG 12.4. Registrar's Office, 1992-1993, undated
  - For the Record, 1992-1993 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, undated (Box 95, Folder 2)
- RG 12.5. Financial Aid, 1923-1925, 1953-2015
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1923-1925, 1953-2015 (Box 95, Folder 3-12, Box 96, Folder 1-9)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 1978-1984 (Box 51, Folder 10, Box 104, Folder 11)
- RG 12.6. Health Services / Health Center, 1957-2003
  - The Student Body, 1995-1996 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - The Vigorous Violet, 1990-1991 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1957-2003 (Box 96, Folder 12-15, Box 97, Folder 1-2)
- RG 12.7. Housing Office, 1990-2003
  - On and Off the Square, 1990 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1960-2003 (Box 97, Folder 4-10)
- RG 12.8. Book Centers / Computer Stores, 1988-2008
  - Bobcat Reader, 1988 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Connect, 2000-2008 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Imprint, 1988-1989 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1970-2010 (Box 98, Folder 1-4)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, undated (Box 104, Folder 12)
- RG 12.9. NYU Card Services, circa 2005
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, circa 2005 (Box 98, Folder 5-6)
- RG 12.10. Center for Multicultural Education and Programs (CMEP), 1987-2018
  - The African Spirit, 1989-1990 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - OAASS Chronicle, 1992 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - The O Line, 2003 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1987-2018 (Box 99, Folder 4-6)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, undated (Box 51, Folder 11)
- RG 12.10.1. Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Scholars Program, 1989-2006
  - The Legacy, 1996-2000 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - The MLK Scholars Journal, 1990-1995 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1989-2006 (Box 99, Folder 9-11, Box 100, Folder 1)
- RG 12.10.2. MLK Celebration Week, 2006-2008
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2006-2008 (Box 100, Folder 2-4)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 2008 (Box 104, Folder 13)
- RG 12.12. Skirball Center for the Performing Arts, 2003-2019
  - NYU Skirball, 2017-2019 (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2003-2017 (Box 100, Folder 5-14, Box 101, Folder 1-2)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 2008-2009, 2017 (Box 104, Folder 15)
- RG 12.13. Student Resource Center, 2006-2010
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2006-2010 (Box 101, Folder 3)
- RG 12.15. Office of Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgender Student Services / LGBTQ Student Center, 2019
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2019 (Box 101, Folder 4)
- RG 12.16. Center for Student Life, 2011
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2011 (Box 101, Folder 5)
- RG 12.18. NYU Leadership Initiative, circa 2016
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, circa 2016 (Box 101, Folder 6)
- RG 13.0. Medical Center (NYU Langone Health), 1970-1971, 2003-2013
  - News and Views, 2003-2018 (Box 48, Folder 9, Box 126, Folder 1)
  - NYU Physician, 2010-2014 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1970-1971 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2010-2012 (Box 101, Folder 9)
- RG 13.6. Office of Public Relations, 1964-1975, 1978-1983
  - New York University Medical Center News, 1964-1975, 1978-1983 (Box 126, Folder 2, Box 127, Folder 1-11)
- RG 13.11. Department of Dermatology, circa 1982
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, circa 1982 (Box 101, Folder 10)
- RG 14.0. University Senate, 1988-2012
  - Faculty Senators Council Newsletter, 2001, 2009 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1988-2012 (Box 101, Folder 12)
- RG 15.2. Faculty Council, 1970-2011
  - Faculty Council Newsletter, 1970-2011 (Box 101, Folder 13, Box 106, Folder 1-4)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1999-2002 (Box 106, Folder 5)
- RG 15.4. Administrative Management Council, 1975
  - Administrative Management Council, 1975 (Box 106, Folder 6)
- RG 15.6. Commission on Undergraduate Education (1971)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1971 (Box 106, Folder 7)
- RG 15.11. Committee of the Staff Council, 1972
  - The Heights Staff Newsletter, 1972 (Box 106, Folder 8)
- RG 15.13. Committee on University Purposes and Guidelines / Hindle Committee, 1971
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1971 (Box 106, Folder 9)
- RG 15.19. Washington Square Council, undated
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, undated (Box 106, Folder 10)
- RG 15.20. EQUAL (Enhancing the Quality of Undergraduate Academic Life) Commission, 1994-2001
  - The Equal Professor, 1994-2001 (Box 106, Folder 11-12)
  - The Equal Professor -- A Faculty Anthology, 1996 (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1995-1998 (Box 106, Folder 14)
- RG 15.21. Community Service Council, 1997-2004
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1997-1998 (Box 106, Folder 15)
- RG 15.23. Association of Lesbian and Gay Faculty, Staff, and Administrators, 1992-1995
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1992-1995 (Box 106, Folder 16)
- RG 15.24. Association of Black Faculty, Administrators and Staff, 1996-1997
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1996-1997 (Box 106, Folder 17)
- RG 15.27. UCATS, Union of Clerical, Administrative and Technical Staff at NYU, Local 3882, circa 2017, undated
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, circa 2017, undated (Box 106, Folder 18)
- RG 16.1. NYU Precollege, 1964, 2001-2017
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1964, 2001-2017 (Box 107, Folder 1-3)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, circa 2011 (Box 102, Folder 7)
- RG 16.2. NYU Summer at Chautauqua, 1948
  - The Chautauquan, 1948 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1948 (Box 107, Folder 4)
- RG 16.3. NYU Freshman Camp, 1940-1945
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1940-1945 (Box 107, Folder 5)
- RG 16.4. University Summer School / NYU Summer Session, 1896-2015
  - Sept. -- Feb. News, 1935-1942 (Box 107, Folder 6-7, Box 108, Folder 1-3)
  - Summer School News, June-August 1916 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Summer Session News of the Week, 1961 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Summer Times, 1935-1936, 1990 (Box 126, Folder 5-8)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1896-1920 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1960-1989 (Box 108, Folder 5-6)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1990-1992, 2000-2015 (Box 431, Folder 1-17, 20-22)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 1970-1989 (Box 102, Folder 7)
- RG 16.5. University Winter Session / NYU Winter Session, 2010-2015
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2010-2015 (Box 431, Folder 18-22)
- RG 16.6 Spring at NYU, 2011
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera (Box 431, Folder 23)
- RG 18.0. University College of Arts and Science, 1915-2008
  - The Geyser, 1926-1928 (Box 109, Folder 1-7, Box 110, Folder 1)
  - College News, 2008 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - The Review, 1941-1945 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1915-1982 (Box 110, Folder 4-15)
- RG 19.0. College of Arts and Science (CAS), 1913-ongoing
  - The Apprentice / Apprentice, 1938-1964 (Box 111, Folder 1-6, Box 126, Folder 9-11)
  - Axis, 1974 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Campus, 1953-1954 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Campus Apprentice, 1956-1958 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - College News, 1995-2017 (Box 111, Folder 10-11)
  - College Newsletter, 1979-1986 (Box 112, Folder 1, Box 126, Folder 12)
  - College of Arts and Science Publications, May 2022-ongoing
    Website containing the CAS Bulletin, Scholar's Lecture, College News, NYU Reads First-year Dialogue, and Inquiry.
  - College of Arts and Science Publications, November 2017-ongoing
  - Counterpoint, 1962-1963 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Chrystalis, 1932 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Dialectic, 1972 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Frosh Frolics, 1951, 1954 (Box 112, Folder 5, Box 126, Folder 13)
  - Inquiry, 1997-2008 (Box 112, Folder 6-7)
  - Inquiry: A Journal of Undergraduate Research, May 2022-ongoing
    Inquiry is the College's journal of undergraduate research, publishing abstracts from the conference and other student work annually. Projects are selected by a faculty committee. The publications date back to 2005.
  - The Journal of the Presidential Scholars, 1987-1989 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Lantern, 1937 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Medusa, 1932 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Mercer Street, 1997-1998, 2005-2007 (Box 112, Folder 10, Box 113, Folder 1-2)
  - Minetta, 1974 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - The Other, 1969 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Salugi, 1966-1967 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Scholar Script: CAS Alumni Scholars, 1989-1990 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Scholars Lecture Series, May 2022-ongoing
  - S.C. Scribe, 1956 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Soph-istication, 1954-1955 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Soph Times, 1950 (Box 126, Folder 15)
  - The Spectator, 1977, 1979 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Washington Square College Review, 1936-1939 (Box 118, Folder 10, Box 119, Folder 1-5, Box 120, Folder 1-3)
  - Washington Square Dealer, 1913-1918 (Box 120, Folder 4, Box 126, Folder 16)
  - Washington Square Review, 1965-1973 (Box 121, Folder 1-7, Box 126, Folder 17)
  - Weinstein Focus, 1968-1969 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - WSC Bulletin, 1957-1965 (Box 120, Folder 6, Box 126, Folder 18)
  - WSC Newsletter, 1964 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - WSC Review, 1961 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1920-1963 (Box 120, Folder 9-12, Box 122, Folder 1-6)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1964-2014 (Box 123, Folder 1-14, Box 124, Box 125, Folder 1-9, Box Shared University Archives 059, Folder 7)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Event Posters, 1970-1980 (Box 126, Folder 19, Box 102, Folder 8)
- RG 19.8. Biology Department, 1979
  - Biology Journal, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Biology Department Development Plan, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 11)
- RG 19.15. Morse Academic Plan, 1997
  - Morse Academic Plan News, 1997 (Box 156, Folder 11)
- RG 20.0. Graduate School of Arts and Science (GSAS), 1894, 1921-2015
  - The Grad Rag, 1978 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science Newsletter, 1994 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Student Newsletter, 1989 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - GSAS Newsletter, 1987-1990 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - G.S.A.S. Reminders, 1965-1971 (Box 129, Folder 5-9)
  - The New York University Series of Graduate School Studies, Volume I, 1914 (Box 194, Folder 8, Box 221, Folder 5)
  - Now: Graduate School of Arts and Science Newsletter, 1974-1977 (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - On the Square, 1994-1997, 2009 (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - Washington Square, 1996 (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, circa 1894 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1921-1940 (Box 130, Folder 2-3)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1965-2015 (Box 130, Folder 4-11, Box 131, Folder 1-3)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, Ephemera, 1973-1986 (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Grants for Graduate Study Booklets, 1980-1991 (Box 131, Folder 4-8)
- RG 20.1. Conservation Center, 1941-2010
  - Conservation Center, 1988-1996 (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - Institute of Fine Arts News, 1943-1969 (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - Marsyas, 1941 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Perspective, 1963 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1935-2010 (Box 132, Folder 3-7, Box 166, Folder 3)
- RG 20.2. Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, 1947-2020